

Arthur JAOUEN

Full Stack Developer

- <u>arthur.jaouen@gmail.com</u> in Linkedin
- Github **(+353)** 89 446 1939

112 Richmond Road

Dublin 3 D03 XC85

Profile

28 years old - Driving licence - French

Having recently moved to Dublin, I am now looking for a company that can provide a great team and Agile experience in a modern development workflow. I love code reviews, unit testing, automated builds and team happiness:)

After a two-year degree in software engineering, I have acquired a solid 6 years work experience centered around the web, mastering diverse frontend and backend technologies. I view myself as a generalist, being able to develop Android applications or React web frontends as well as PHP, Ruby or .Net backends. Passionate about open-source software, I like to try leading-edge technologies such as Rust or Elm and apply the lessons learned to my everyday code.

This CV is powered by React, Typescript, SCSS and built by Webpack.

View source on Github

♥ Interests

- projects Personal projects
- t Chess
- Windsurf
- Reading

(B) Work experience



February 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 8 months)

Full Stack Developer (React, Android, .Net)

Java JS C# HTML/CSS • Android React .Net • SQLServer

SQLite

Comerso's goal is to help retail and industry adopt a zero-waste strategy with a strong technological approach. Comerso provides multiple solutions to handle the end of life of retail products:

- Logistics to donate products to non-profit organizations
- · Tools to help donate, track due dates and edit discounts for products
- A portal to monitor and manage the end of life of products

As a team of four developers we worked in a scrum environment, and built up a modern continuous integration workflow based on Azue DevOps. As a full stack developer, I worked on various applications:

- The REST API backend (C#, .Net, .Net Core)
- The internal administration frontend (React, Typescript)
- C-Stats customer portal (React, Typescript)
- Comerso android app, to track due dates and edit discounts for
- GefMobile android app, to track logistics between retailers and nonprofit endpoints

January 2016 - March 2016 (3 months)



Full Stack Developer (PHP, Angular, Cordova)

PHP JS HTML/CSS • Bootstrap Angular Cordova • MySQL Solr

Implementation of a mobile app to display a catalog of products for a large aeronautics industrial company:

- · PHP REST API to manage and query the catalog
- Cordova mobile app (Android and iOS) to view the catalog
- November 2015 December 2015 (2 months)



Backend Developer (Ruby)

Ruby • Ruby on Rails • SQLServer

Implementation of a REST API for the company ITG using Ruby on Rails:

- · User and client authentication
- Mapping of an existing SQL Server database
- Unit and functional testing
- September 2015 October 2015 (2 months)

Full Stack Developer (PHP, Javascript)

PHP JS HTML/CSS • Bootstrap jQuery • MySQL Solr

Implementation of a customer portal for the accounting company BDO:

- Dashboard with KPIs for agents and customers
- Integration of an existing EDM
- Messaging interface between agents and customers
- Timeline with actions to perform for the customers

April 2011 - May 2015 (4 years 2 months)



Full Stack Developer

PHP Java Ruby Python JS HTML/CSS • Symfony Rails Android

MySQL PostgreSQL SQLServer

Enterprise service around open source software:

- · Web and Android applications development
- Custom plugin development for open-source software (OpenERP, Alfresco, OCS Inventory, GLPI, Redmine)
- Reporting (Talend, Pentaho)
- Trainings (OCS Inventory, GLPI)
- Member of the OCS Inventory core team

Education

2008 - 2011

Two-year degree in <u>Computer</u> <u>Science</u>

At the <u>Lannion Institue of Technology (France)</u> with an emphasis on software engineering

2008

Science A-levels

With an emphasis on mathematics and engineering sciences



Frontend development



Languages

French English Spanish Italian ★★★★ ★★★☆ ★☆☆☆☆ ★☆☆☆☆